everyone, I'm Marco, the Product Innovation Lead at Applied AI Lab.
Today, I'll walk you through how Pencil,
our AI-powered English writing platform,
helps you create assignments, create essays,
analyze data, all in one place.
Whether you're a teacher of primary school,
secondary school, or pencil-has-your-back. First,
log into the platform. It's super easy to create a new essay assignment.
Just enter the essay tag, essay topic,
then select your grading format, TSA,
DSE writing, listening, or even customized rubric.
I then select the class, the due date of the essay assignment, and the
language difficulty of the graded report.
And don't forget, generate the pre-writing guide.
I will then be able to utilize the materials in my lessons beforehand.
The pre-writing guide contains information about the text type,
the ideas for the essay, and the structure of the essay,
as well as some vocabulary generated according to the essay topic.
Everything here on the pre-writing guide are all editable and
their account, with all the information about the essay,
including the due date and the pre-writing guide.
Upon completion, students have flexible options to submit their essay.
If they prefer typing, they can use the built-in editor.
If they've written their essay by hand, they can simply take a photo or
upload a PDF. Our OCR function converts handwriting to digital text
with up to 97% accuracy.
They can also adjust page order and preview everything before submitting,
just in one click.
and organization. Clearly marks errors and suggests revision.
Highlights strengths and areas for improvement.
With tailored grammar and sentence rewriting exercise.
And a piece of enhanced essay for the student to refer to.
Teachers can also manually adjust the score and check the original submission.
Making grading faster, smarter, and more reliable.
also automatically aggregates data on a class-wide basis.
The Common Error Report highlights the most frequent grammatical and vocabulary issues.
It also generates exercises like fill-in-the-blanks exercises and sentence rewriting exercises.
It highlights good sentences for teachers to share in class,
so instead of guessing, your teaching is now guided by real
Pencil helps you track each student's individual progress,
with graphs showing their scores across content,
language, and organization through time. Performance history of each essay assignment easily
spots trends like improvements or repeated issues.
This allows me to track to customize instructions and intervene whenever it's needed.
ask questions like, is this sentence correct?
Or how can I improve this? The AI will instantly analyze the sentence,
provide a better phrasing, and even summarize the mistakes.
It's not just about finishing the essay,
it's about learning to write better.
From assignment creation to grading analysis and self-directed learning,
Pencil fully digitizes and AI enhances your daily teaching workflow.
It saves you time, helps you teach better,
and helps you still do an improved faster. Once you experience AI powered writing
instructions, Pencil is the tool for you.
if you have any questions regarding to our Pencil AI application,
feel free to reach out to us for more information.